<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.simplifide.features"
      label="Simplifide"
      version="1.2.30.qualifier"
      provider-name="SIMPLIFIDE">

   <description url="http://www.example.com/description">
      Support for hardware langages
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      Copyright © 2007-2010 Simplifide
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      Software License Agreement and Limited Warranty 
This is a legal agreement (this &amp;apos;License&amp;apos;) between you, 
the end user, and SimplifIDE
Opening the enclosed disk envelope or, if electronically 
distributed, downloading and using the Software indicates 
that you accept and agree to comply with these terms. 
If you do not agree to these terms, (a) you may so notify 
SimplifIDE. within thirty (30) days of downloading for a full 
refund, or (b) you may write to SimplifIDE. with a request 
to modify any term of this License. Please allow six 
(6) weeks for a response.

1. GRANT OF LICENSE. SimplifIDE grants to you a non-exclusive, 
personal license to use the Software as provided in this 
License. Each permitted copy of the Software may be stored 
in memory (either temporary or &amp;apos;permanent&amp;apos;), on no more than 
one computer at any one time. However, you may install the 
Software on a network server for the sole purpose of valid 
distribution to other computers.
IT IS STRICTLY PROHIBITED TO refer your registration number to third 
parties if you are a registered user.

2. COPYRIGHT. The Software is owned by SimplifIDE or its 
suppliers and is protected by United States copyright laws 
and international treaty provisions. This means that you 
must treat the Software like a book, musical recording or 
any other copyrighted material. Nevertheless, SimplifIDE
gives you the right to (a) make two copies of the 
Software solely for backup or archival purposes, or 
(b) transfer the Software to a single hard disk, provided 
you keep the original solely for backup or archival purposes. 
You may not copy the written materials accompanying the 
Software (called the &amp;apos;Documentation&amp;apos;). You should be 
aware that illegal copying or distribution of copyrighted 
material is investigated by the FBI, and is punishable by 
prison terms of up to 10 years. 

3. OTHER RESTRICTIONS. You may not rent or lease the 
Software, but you may permanently transfer the Software 
and Documentation provided you retain no copies and the 
recipient agrees to the terms of this Agreement. You may 
not modify, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, or 
create derivative works from the Software or Documentation.
IF software includes SOURCE CODE, You may NOT make Software 
SOURCE CODE publically or freely available. If SOFTWARE is BETA or PROMOTIONAL,
You may not resell or re-distribute it.

4. TERM. This License is effective until terminated. 
You may terminate the license at any time by returning 
the Software and all Documentation to SimplifIDE and by 
removing the Software from the memory of the computer 
into which the Software has been transferred. This 
License may be terminated by SimplifIDE immediately and 
without notice in the event that you fail to comply 
with any term or condition hereof. Upon any termination, 
you will return to SimplifIDE, at your expense, the 
Software and Documentation and any copies whether or not 
the copying was authorized. Should you fail to comply with any 
of the above-mentioned your user&amp;apos;s rights would be automatically 
terminated. This termination will be in addition to any 
criminal, civil or other remedies.

5. EXPORT LAW ASSURANCES. You agree that neither the 
Software nor any direct product thereof is being or 
will be acquired, shipped, transferred, or reexported, 
directly or indirectly, into any country prohibited 
by the United States Export Administration Act and 
the regulations thereunder or will be used for any 
purpose prohibited by the same.

6. SEVERABILITY. If for any reason, any provision 
or partial provision of this License is held invalid, 
such invalidity shall not affect the remainder of 
such provision or this License, and this License 
shall, to the full extent consistent with law, 
continue in full force and effect.

7. GENERAL. The validity and performance of this 
License shall be governed by United States law, 
except for that body of law dealing with conflict 
of laws and except as to copyrights, which are 
governed by United States laws and international 
treaties. This License constitutes the entire 
agreement between the parties concerning the 
subject matter hereof. Any waiver or amendment 
of any provision of this License shall be 
effective only if in writing and signed by you 
and an officer of SimplifIDE No distributor, 
dealer, or employee (other than an officer) 
of SimplifIDE. is authorized to change or amend 
any terms of this License. In the event of any 
conflict between the terms of this License and 
the terms of any license bound into any manual 
packaged with the Software, this License shall 
govern.
LIMITED WARRANTY
SimplifIDE. warrants that for thirty (30) days 
following delivery of the Software to you: 
(1) the Software, unless modified by you, will 
perform substantially the functions described in 
the Documentation provided by SimplifIDE.; and 
(2) the media on which the Software is furnished 
will be free from defects in materials and 
workmanship under normal use.
SimplifIDE. does not 
warrant that the Software will meet your 
requirements or that operation of the Software 
will be uninterrupted or error-free. SimplifIDE. 
is not responsible for any problem, including 
any problem which would otherwise be a breach 
of warranty, caused by (i) changes in the 
operating characteristics of computer hardware 
or computer operating systems which are made 
after the release of the Software, 
(ii) interaction of the Software with non-SimplifIDE. 
software or (iii) accident, abuse, or misapplication.
THE ABOVE WARRANTIES ARE MADE BY SIMPLIFIDE. 
ALONE, AND THEY ARE THE ONLY WARRANTIES MADE 
BY ANYONE REGARDING THE ENCLOSED SOFTWARE. 
SIMPLIFIDE. AND ITS LICENSOR(S) MAKE NO OTHER 
WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING 
WITHOUT LIMITATION THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES 
OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A 
PARTICULAR PURPOSE, REGARDING THE ENCLOSED 
SOFTWARE. EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE EXPRESSLY 
PROVIDED ABOVE, SIMPLIFIDE. AND ITS LICENSOR(S) 
DO NOT WARRANT, GUARANTEE OR MAKE ANY 
REPRESENTATION REGARDING THE USE OR THE 
RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE SOFTWARE IN TERMS 
OF ITS CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, 
CURRENTNESS, OR OTHERWISE. THE ENTIRE RISK 
AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF THE 
SOFTWARE IS ASSUMED BY YOU. THE EXCLUSION 
OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES IS NOT PERMITTED BY 
SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS, SO THE ABOVE 
EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN THAT 
CASE, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES ARE LIMITED 
IN DURATION TO THIRTY (30) DAYS FROM THE 
DATE OF DELIVERY OF THE SOFTWARE. THERE MAY 
BE OTHER RIGHTS THAT YOU MAY HAVE WHICH VARY 
FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION.
LIMITATION OF REMEDIES
SimplifIDE.&amp;apos;s entire liability and your sole remedy under 
the warranty during the thirty (30) day warranty period 
is that SimplifIDE. shall, at its sole and exclusive 
option, either replace the Software with a functionally 
equivalent program at no charge to you or refund the 
license fee of the Software. Any replacement Software 
will be warranted for the remainder of the original 
warranty period or thirty (30) days, whichever is 
longer. These are your sole and exclusive remedies for 
any breach of warranty during this ninety (90) day 
period.
REGARDLESS OF WHETHER OR NOT ANY REMEDY SET 
FORTH HEREIN FAILS OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE, 
IN NO EVENT WILL SIMPLIFIDE., ITS LICENSOR(S) 
AND THE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES OR 
AGENTS OF ANY OF THEM BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR 
ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR INDIRECT 
DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF 
BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, 
LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, AND THE LIKE) 
ARISING OUT THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE 
THE SOFTWARE EVEN IF SIMPLIFIDE. OR ITS LICENSOR(S) 
HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH 
DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS 
DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF 
LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL 
DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY 
TO YOU. SIMPLIFIDE. AND ITS LICENSOR(S) LIABILITY 
TO YOU FOR ACTUAL DAMAGES FROM ANY CAUSE 
WHATSOEVER, AND REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF 
THE ACTION (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT [INCLUDING 
NEGLIGENCE], PRODUCT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE), 
WILL BE LIMITED TO $50.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Simplifide" url="http://simplifide.com/html/updates"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="com.simplifide.base"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.30.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.simplifide.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.30.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.simplifide.scala2"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.30.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.simplifide.generator"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.2.30.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
